valueapplications.com 2009-03-04

# Legal Agreement

Go Daddy is a licensee of the [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) Privacy Program. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Go Daddy at [privacy@godaddy.com](mailto:privacy@godaddy.com) or call (480) 505-8800. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. However, please understand the [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) Privacy Program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site. 

**Go Daddy complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. We will respond to your request for access to modify or delete your information within thirty (30) days.**

**We will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.**

Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (your name, address, daytime telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, request information and support, and make product suggestions. We will then create an account number for you and if you choose to order from us using a credit card, we will collect your credit card number and expiration date. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given. We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our web site, new Go Daddy services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the "Updating Your Information" section below on how to change your preferences. If we present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

On rare occasions, one of our partners may require us to share your personal information with them. We will only do so with your explicit permission first. 

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We use [cookies](https://www.godaddy.com/gdshop/secure.asp) to identify you so you don't have to login each time you visit our site. They are linked to your customer number which is associated with the information in your account. 

This site also contains links to other sites. Unfortunately Go Daddy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**For Go Daddy Marketplace Customers Only**

When you purchase goods through Go Daddy Marketplace, you are granting Go Daddy express permission to share your name and contact information (as well as the “ship to” name and contact information, if different) with the merchant from which you make the purchase, for the purposes of shipping and order fulfillment only. By making a purchase from a merchant, you are not granting that merchant consent to use your information for marketing or any other purposes unless you specifically “opt in” to do so. Go Daddy has agreements with the merchants on Go Daddy Marketplace requiring them to maintain the privacy of your information; however, Go Daddy is not responsible for improper use by merchants of your information. 

When you create a storefront to offer goods for sale through Go Daddy Marketplace, you will be prompted to enter information about your business, including business name, e-mail address and telephone number (all mandatory), and address, fax number and business hours (all optional). The business information that you enter will be publicly displayed on your storefront page, and will be included in confirmation e-mails sent to people who make purchases from you. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please view our [Secure Ordering](https://www.godaddy.com/gdshop/secure.asp) page for further details. 

**Updating Your Information**

As a customer of Go Daddy, you may alter your customer information or opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at any time. We have the following options for changing and modifying your customer information. 

| 

**Sending Emails**

We use emails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links, as on our ["About Go Daddy"](https://www.godaddy.com/gdshop/about.asp) page, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to promptly reply to your messages. 

The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. However, your information will only be shared with third parties with your explicit permission. 

**Only If We Have To**

As stated previously in this policy, we will not share your personal information except with a third party to assist us in the processing or securing of your personal information or when we are required by law unless we have given you notice and choice, in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our web site. We will share your information in order to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies. We may also need to give out your information if one of our partners requires it, but these situations are rare. 

**Changes in Our Practices**

If we make material changes to our information handling practices or other privacy policies, we will post those changes on this privacy statement, or notify you directly via email, at least 30 days prior to their implementation. Minor changes will be immediately effective upon reposting to this privacy statement on the Go Daddy Web site. 

**Service Provider**

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Contest**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level – you must be 18 or above to enter). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
